[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "Does that sum up Michael Moore?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "Well, I'm a citizen of this country.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Moore"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "FOX, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "CC", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "People are always cynical at first whenever there's a movement for -- or a protest that's starting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["New Yorkers"]}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "What kind of people are they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "Not New Yorkers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "Are they -- what are they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Well, there's no -- I didn't meet any ex-bankers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "I mean this is the wrong way for the American dream to work, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "That's correct.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "What did you think of that protest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "I don't think it was a -- I don't know if it was a protest.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "There has to be -- there has to be a control over this, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "No -- no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 153, "question": "Where is your line drawn in active protesting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "Well --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "You wouldn't endorse looting, would you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "No, no, of course not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "When you saw Obama's jobs plan come out, do you have any confidence it's gong to work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "Has he failed in not doing this before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "Who are the bad guys, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 204, "question": "And we don't, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "But tell me this --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "And he's not going to come on and sit here and talk to you, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", "NN", "RB", "CC", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "No, we've asked him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Is it really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "You've got a company.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "Well -- isn't it in its purest sense?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Well, Piers, there's nothing pure about capitalism.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "What is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "First of all, I do well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 234, "question": "Is there a good form of capitalism?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "Well --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Has it simply been corrupted?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "It's like saying -- you know, when you say the word capitalism, you have to talk about it in its current sense.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "Where did it go wrong?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "It went wrong because people -- first of all, we started rewarding people not for making things or inventing things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "Do you concede to either?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "The first part of that -- I plead guilty to the dangerous part maybe.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "Do you have any views that you think are genuinely surprising to people who just think you are a predictable knee-jerk liberal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "I could tell you things that I agree with conservatives on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party", "Republican Party"]}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "EX", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "I mean do you have a blanket distrust and hatred of all things Tea Party or can you recognize that some things they say are completely reasonable and that's why they gather support?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "At the very beginning there might have been some people who were trying to join the Tea Party to say some reasonable things because they were upset at Wall Street and what was happening, but these days, no, the Tea Party is a wing of the Republican Party thinking, it's funded by billionaires.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Do you think CNN would do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "ORGAN: Well, I don't know but --", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CNN"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "Well, how about a CNN/Teachers union debate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "I would have a debate with you tomorrow.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Why has he pissed it away?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "I don't -- I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "Who -- to you who was the least worrying Republican candidate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "TO", "PRP", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "VBG", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Well, there's only one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "Why isn't he getting the traction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Have you struggled to sleep at night with the idea that any one of those might have been innocent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "No, sir, I've never struggled with that at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "Getting applause for defending Texas' record on capital punishment, which is -- you know, is it something worth applauding in the modern age, Michael?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "Well, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"], "LOCATION": ["Texas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "Do you think Americans know how few other countries actually have the death penalty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNPS", "RB", "WRB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "No, I don't think they do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "Why don't you think they do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "OORE: And I don't think they know where we stand in terms of how many people we execute.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "-- that to me is the end of the debate, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "It should absolutely be the end of the debate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "How do you change that thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "That's a good question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["Osama"]}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "WP", "NNP", "VBD", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "JJS", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "What would you have done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "I would have done exactly what Obama did and use our special forces, who are some of our smartest and best trained soldiers, to begin the effort to track down Osama bin Laden and his lieutenants and bring them to justice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Flint"]}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "Would you be willing to come up with us and see what the situation is like in Flint for people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "I've been to Flint.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Flint"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Flint"]}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "TO", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "Could you come up to Flint with us?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "I cannot come up to Flint, I'm sorry.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Flint"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "Where did it come from?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Pretty well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "I would say vindicated, but I'm expecting that some people wouldn't agree, but I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Do you have moments of, I don't want to do this any more?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "Did you think you were going to die?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Nancy Grace"]}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", ":", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "You could kill me with a piece of dental floss?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "Right now, I could -- this show would suddenly belong to Nancy Grace.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CBS"], "PERSON": ["Janet Jackson"]}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNP", "VBZ", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "Where are they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "Janet Jackson bares a breast and CBS is fined God knows how much money and yet he can say that over the air and encourage the unhinged to harm me like that, and nothing happens.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "I just thought how can a guy who hosts a show call for literally want to kill somebody like you for expressing a political opinion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "Yeah, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 711, "question": "What happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 712, "answer": "I begged my parents to go to the seminary.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 722, "question": "He wasn't wrong, was he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 723, "answer": "He was kicking me out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "Well, of course, you could be -- you could be in favor of that way or in favor of men.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NN", "IN", ":", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 731, "question": "Did you genuinely sit there one day and think, I either never have sex again or I have to stop my plan to be a priest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "CD", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 732, "answer": "No, I think I sort of -- puberty kicked in a little late on me, but it kicked in there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 747, "question": "Do you have groupies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 748, "answer": "No, I don't have groupies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 751, "question": "You have the love of a good woman?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 752, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 757, "question": "True love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 758, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 772, "question": "What has been the greatest moment of your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 773, "answer": "Wow!", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 777, "question": "You mean if I could do it again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 778, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 786, "question": "How long was that drive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 787, "answer": "Seven hundred fifty miles.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bob Dylan", "Joan Baez"], "LOCATION": ["Quebec City", "Michigan"]}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 789, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 790, "answer": "I drove 900 miles to Quebec City to see Bob Dylan and Joan Baez in concert because that was the closest place they were playing to Michigan on that tour.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 792, "question": "Do you accept you're slightly mad in that case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 793, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 798, "question": "Go see David Letterman, 750 miles?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 799, "answer": "Completely crackers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Letterman"]}}]